Oh! I'm glad you're here,
Bushy Brow!
おう！ よく来たな ゲジマユ！
Everyone! Now that I'm here,
you have nothing to fear!
皆さん！ ボクが来たからには
もう安心ですよ！
Hey!
ちょっと！ 私たちがでしょ！
アンタ 張り切りすぎ！
It's "we're here". You are too eager.
Well, you can relax.
フフン まぁ
大船に乗った気でいなさいよ。
You're as confident as always,
相変わらず強気だけど
医療忍術のイロハは➡
but have you mastered
the ABCs of Medical Ninjutsu?
マスターできたのかしら？
なんですって!?
What?! For someone who started
Medical Ninjutsu just a tad before me,
ちょっと先に修業始めたからって
ずいぶん強気じゃない。
you sound pretty confident yourself.
Well sure. It's not as though
I started yesterday.
えぇ 昨日今日
かじった人とは違うわよ。
Well, you need that handicap.
そのくらいのハンデがなきゃね。
After all, we're not equals,
Billboard Brow.
アンタと私は
互角じゃないんだから。
デコデコちゃん。
は～っ!?
I haven't been called that
in a while... Ino Pig!
懐かしいこと
言ってんじゃないわよ！
いのブタが！
なんですって!?
What?!
So their nicknames are
Billboard Brow and Ino Pig...?
２人のニックネームは
デコデコと いのブタ… と。
Huh?
ぐはっ！
What... did... I...?
いったい ボクが… 何か…。
Tsunade-sama briefed us on the basics.
綱手様から だいたいの話は
聞いているけど➡
But can you give us the specifics
of the situation?
改めて 状況を説明してください。
Well, there's a new development...
そうだな
新たな展開もあるし。
- What's with him?
- Let's do our best!
What did I do?
What were you writing?
Let's see it.
Yes... We'll explain over there.
じゃあ
あちらで話しましょう。
There are four Shinobi who can
move freely inside a smoke screen.
敵は 煙幕の中で
自在に行動できる忍４人。
Also, the big guy I fought,
and then there's a Crystal Style user...
オレと戦った大男が一人
そして 晶遁使い。
They were in the lake dealing
with a Tailed Beast
湖で ヤツらは 三尾と思われる
尾獣と接触しています。
which we believe is a Three-Tails.
Hmm... That was included
in our information.
うん そこまでは 情報どおりね。
Well, we'd better get started quickly
so we can seal it.
では こちらも
すぐ封印に とりかからないと。
If the enemy takes possession of
the Three-Tails' fighting power,
三尾の戦力が敵に渡ったら
やっかいだわ。
we're in trouble.
There's one more thing...
a new development.
さらに もうひとつ➡
新たな状況が生まれている。
え？
Huh?!
Naruto witnessed a child
at the lake.
湖で ナルトが
一人の子供を目撃している。
And he says that child
controls the Tailed Beast.
その子供が 尾獣を
操っているように見えたらしい。
No way... Someone who can
control a Tailed Beast...?
まさか…。
尾獣を操れる者がいるなんて。
Furthermore, Naruto later encountered
the child with the Crystal Style user.
しかも その後 ナルトは
晶遁使いと子供と接触している。
What's their relationship?
その２人の関係は？
主従に近い。
It seems they're quite close...
Naruto says, "the Crystal Style user is
the place where the child can return to".
ナルト風に話せば➡
晶遁使いが 子供の
帰るべき場所ってヤツらしい。
Just who is this child?
その子供は いったい何者なの？
The Three-Tails doesn't have
a Jinchuriki...
三尾に人柱力はいないはず。
Not yet...
After all, we're dealing with Orochimaru.
それは まだ…。
しかし 大蛇丸のことです。
Maybe he's aiming to make
that child a Jinchuriki.
その子を人柱力にしようと
狙っているのかもしれません。
It seems we have yet another
troubling thing to deal with.
やっかいごとが
ひとつ増えたみたいね。
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and i'll never take it for granted
let's go
Regroup!
(鬼霧)人間相手なら ともかくだ。
We knew we had to deal
with human foes,
尾獣が相手とは
聞いちゃいないぜ アニキ。
but no one said a thing about
a Tailed Beast!
(鬼鳳)あぁ 確かに。
No kidding. That thing caused
a huge flood just by appearing.
現れただけで あんな大洪水を
起こすヤツを相手に➡
いったい 何を
おっぱじめようってんだ？
What the hell are they starting?
(濡羅吏)でも 私たち 今さら
逃げられないんじゃないの？
But it's too late for us to run away.
(鬼鳳)なぁ オレたちが
抜けられる方法を考えてくれよ。
Say, think of a way we can get out of this.
(鬼霧)せっかく あの収容所から
生きて抜け出せた命を➡
We were lucky to make it
out of that camp alive.
みすみす化け物のために
放り出したくないぜ。
I'm not about to give my life
to some damned beast!
(濡羅吏)ねぇ
頼りにしてるんだから 麟児。
We're counting on you, Rinji.
《麟児 : どこまで
おめでたいヤツらだ…》
Just how simple are
these guys anyway?
悪いようにはしない。
あとは オレに任せておけ。
Look, I'll work things out.
Leave the rest to me.
(濡羅吏)さすが 麟児！
Just as I expected, Rinji!
どこへ行く？
Where are you going?
紅蓮さんに報告なら
オレがやっとく。
If you're going to report to Guren-san,
I'll go.
(牛頭)オレは お前のことを
信用できない。
I can't trust you...
オメエが どう思おうが 自由だがよ。
Well, how you feel is up to you.
紅蓮さんも裏切るつもりか？
Do you intend to betray Guren-san?
答え次第では 許さない。
Whether I forgive you or not
depends on your answer...
フッ 存外 オレは
紅蓮さんには忠実なんだよ。
Contrary to what you believe,
my loyalties are with Guren-san.
それは… どうかな…。
I wonder... about that...
ここだけの話だけどよ➡
This is just between you and me...
なぜ オレが ここにいると思う？
Why do you think I'm here?
里に 体の弱い妹を
残しているんだ。
I left a sickly kid sister back
in the village...
ソイツを守ってやるために
カネがいるんだよ。
In order to protect her, I need money.
だからよ ここで命を
落とすわけにはいかねえんだ。
That's why...
I can't afford to lose my life here.
この話をどうとろうが
オメエの勝手だがな。
What you make of my story
is totally up to you.
あっ！
Oh?
起きたかい？
You're up?
紅蓮さんは？
Where's Guren-san?
ん？ あぁ…。
Oh...
どうだい？ 大蛇丸様のもとへ
戻ってみるかい？
How about it?
Want to go back to Orochimaru-sama?
紅蓮さんも一緒？
Will Guren-san come with us?
紅蓮？
Guren...? She's just a sacrifice
to Orochimaru-sama...
ヤツは 大蛇丸様にとっては
捨て駒だからね。
Huh?!
忘れるんじゃない。
キミは 大蛇丸様のものなんだよ。
Don't forget...
You belong to Orochimaru-sama.
イヤだ！ ボクの帰るところは
紅蓮さんのいるところな…。
No! The place I return to...
is the place where Guren-san is--!
うわっ！ あっ！
幽鬼丸から離れな！
紅蓮さん！
Move away from Yuukimaru!
Guren-san!
この子に何するつもりだ？
What do you intend to do to him?!
なに… ちょっと
しつけてやっただけだよ。
I'm... just disciplining him a bit.
今 幽鬼丸に何かあったら
困るのは ボクだからね。
I'm the one who's gonna be
in trouble with Orochimaru-sama
if anything should happen
to Yuukimaru.
大蛇丸様の期待を
裏切ることはできないよ。
I mustn't disappoint him.
まともにしゃべることも
できなかったのに➡
He wasn't able to even talk properly.
よく ここまで仕込んだもんだね。
I'm amazed at how much
you've taught him.
今度 幽鬼丸に
手を上げるようなマネをしたら➡
If you ever lay a hand on Yuukimaru again,
I'll show you no mercy.
アンタだって容赦しないよ。
フン！ せいぜい
実験体を守ってくれよ。
Humph! Well then...
Keep a good eye on our test subject.
フン…。
大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
うん！ ボクは
紅蓮さんと一緒だよね？
Uh-huh! I'm going to stay
with you, right?
紅蓮さん もうアジトへは
帰りたくないよ。
Guren-san... I don't want to go back
to the hideout.
麟児か？
Rinji...?
フッ まさかあの
大蛇丸様命の堅物女が➡
Can you believe that?
She was so hung up on
Orochimaru-sama and now it's the kid...
ガキなんかに転ぶとは…➡
任務に支障がなきゃ
いいんですが➡
I hope it doesn't interfere
with her mission...
肩入れしすぎなのが
気がかりですね。
I'm worried that she's getting
a bit too attached to him.
ここは 大蛇丸様に
お伺いをたてておくか。
Well, we'll just leave her
to Orochimaru-sama.
お前は ヤツがおかしな考えを
起こさないよう➡
I want you to continue
to watch her closely...
引き続き 監視を続けてくれ。
and make sure she's not up to anything.
引き続き… か。
Continue... eh?
オレが 大蛇丸様への連絡役を
やってもいいんですけどね。
I'd be happy to be the one reporting
to Orochimaru-sama...
ん？ お前が？
You?
オレは アンタの草として
ずいぶん働いてきた。
I've done many things for you
as your spy.
囚人のフリをして アジトの
改造人間たちの間に紛れ込み➡
I posed as a convict at that prison and
got accepted by those reconstructed men
逐一 様子を連絡するっていう
危険な仕事もこなしてきた。
and sent you reports.
That was dangerous work.
今度のことだって
オレが命をはってるからこそ➡
Even this job...
It's because I'm putting my life
at risk like this...
こうして 欲しい情報が
手に入ってるってわけですよね？
that you're able to get
the data you want.
何が言いたい？
What are you trying to say?
単純なことですよ➡
It's simple. I want you to value me
a little bit more.
もう少し オレを評価して
いただけませんかね？
取り引きのつもりか？
You want to cut a deal?
そんな 取り引きですって？
No such thing...
オレは 前々から カブトさん
アンタの部下だとは思っちゃいない。
I've never considered myself
to be your subordinate.
オレは 大蛇丸様の配下なんだ。
I serve Orochimaru-sama.
ほう。
なあに オレの働きを➡
Oh...
I just want Orochimaru-sama himself
to recognize my efforts.
大蛇丸様に 直接
認めていただきたいだけですよ。
少なくとも この場所では➡
At least here, in this location,
鬼霧 鬼鳳 濡羅吏の３人を
動かせる➡
I'm the one who can get Kigiri, Kihou
and Nurari to act.
オレのほうが
アンタよりは 戦力は上だ。
I have more fighting power than you.
なんだったら まず➡
I mean, if you're the one who's killed
by the Hidden Leaf first,
カブトさんが 木ノ葉に殺されたって
第一報を持って➡
大蛇丸様のアジトに走っても
いいんですけどね。
I can rush to Orochimaru-sama
and report it to him.
わかった。 会わせてやる。
All right, I'll let you see him.
しかし 身の丈にあまる
野望を持つと➡
But if you don't keep
your expectations realistic,
自分を滅ぼすことになるよ。
you'll end up being destroyed...
いいか？ しばらく
表は騒がしくなるからね➡
Now listen. It's going to get noisy
outside for a bit.
ここで
おとなしく待っているんだ。
Just be a good boy and wait here.
紅蓮さんは？
ヤボ用が終わったら➡
What about you, Guren-san?
As soon as I take care of some business,
I will come back. I promise.
必ず帰ってくるから➡
お前は 体を休めることだけ
考えてりゃいいんだ。
All you need to think about
is resting your body.
もう大丈夫だよ
少し楽になったから。
I'm okay. I feel a little better.
まだまだ ちゃんと治すんだよ。
No, not yet.
You need to heal completely.
あのね お願いがあるんだ。
Umm... I want to ask you for a favor...
これ 直してほしくて。
Can you... fix this?
あぁ。
I see...
直すより もっといいのを
作ってやるよ。
Rather than fixing this,
I'll make you a better one.
でも…。
どうした？
But...
What's the matter?
やっぱり それがいい！
I want to keep this one.
This is the first flower you gave me...
紅蓮さんが
初めてくれた花だから。
そうか。
Oh right...
さっ 直ったぞ。
ありがとう。
Here, it's fixed.
Thank you.
あのね どこにも行かないよね？
Umm, you won't go anywhere, right?
えっ!?
Huh...?
ボクが帰るのは 紅蓮さんのところ。
The place I return to is with you...
《バカなことを…。
This is stupid...
私は 何をしているんだ？
いったい》
Just what... am I doing?
ナルト。
Naruto...
カカシ先生。
どうした？ 何考えてる？
Kakashi-sensei...
What's the matter?
What's on your mind?
うん…。
アイツ！ もう作戦会議が
始まるっていうのに➡
That guy!
The strategy meeting has begun.
どこ ほっつき歩いてるんだか。
What's keeping him?!
ナルトのことになると
怒りっぱなし… と。
She's always upset when
it comes to Naruto...
あっ。
どうしました？
Huh...?
ナルト 見つかったんですか？
シッ！
What's the matter?
Did you find Naruto?
アイツを どうするつもりなんだ？
What do you plan on doing
with that kid?
どうしてそこまで
その子のことを気にするんだ？
Why're you so worried about him?
アイツは 利用されてるんだ！
He's being used!
いつか帰るべき場所だって
信じてるヤツに必ず…➡
He believes there's someone
he can return to...
必ず 裏切られる。
But he's sure to be betrayed.
そうなったら アイツ
帰る場所がなくなっちまうんだ。
When that happens...
He won't have anywhere to go.
思っている人がいるところが
帰るべき場所だっていうんなら➡
If wherever someone thinks of you
is the place you return to...
オレは オレが アイツのことを
思い続けてやる。
Then... I'll keep thinking of him.
《前に言ってた話
サスケ君のことじゃなかったんだ》
Then he wasn't talking about Sasuke-kun...
人が 人を思うってことは
大切かもしれない。
It may be important to think
about people.
だけど そう上手くいくかな。
But I wonder if things always
go that smoothly?
人の思いは それぞれだからね。
After all, everyone has
different thoughts and feelings.
そんなことはねえ！
That's not true.
Feelings always get through to others!
思いは きっと通じる！
ナルト…。
Naruto...
では これより
綱手様の指令により➡
Let me go over Tsunade-sama's orders
今後の作戦と
班編成の変更を伝えます。
regarding strategy and a change
in team formation.
大蛇丸のアジト探索 および
その援護の任務は➡
The search-and-aid mission
to Orochimaru's hideout is now over.
現時点をもって終了とする。
サクラ ヒナタ いの あなたたちは
私の指令下に。
Sakura, Hinata and Ino...
you will be under my command.
(ヒナタ/サクラ)はい。
はい。
- Yes.
あとの人は 改めて カカシさんの
指令の下に入ることになるわ。
Yes.
Kakashi-san will lead the rest.
うん 綱手様からの新たな任務は
尾獣 三尾の封印➡
Right. Our new mission is to seal
the Tailed Beast, the Three-Tails.
そして なんらかの形で➡
And, to protect the child from the enemy.
尾獣と関わっていると思われる
子供を➡
敵から保護することだ。
He seems to be connected in
some way to this Tailed Beast.
尾獣を狙っているのは
暁だけではない。
Huh?!
It is not just the Akatsuki who
covet the Tailed Beast.
人柱力のいない尾獣が
出現したとなれば➡
If it becomes known that there is
a Tailed Beast that has no Jinchuriki,
各国こぞって その捕獲に
乗り出すだろうからな。
other nations are bound to join the hunt.
その子 人柱力にするために
連れてこられたんだね ナルト。
So that boy was brought here to turn him
into a Jinchuriki?
Right, Naruto?
サイ！
あぁ ナルトも人柱力でしたね。
- Huh?
- Sai!
Huh? Oh right...
You're a Jinchuriki too, Naruto.
ヘッ オメエってば
相変わらず 空気読めねえヤツだな。
Humph.
You always say things without thinking.
だけど 言ってることは
そのとおりだ。
Still, you're right about what you said.
三尾の封印も
あの子を保護するのも➡
Sealing the Three-Tails
and protecting that kid...
オレや 我愛羅みてえなのを
出さないための作戦➡
That's so he doesn't end up
like Gaara and me, right, Shizune onee-chan?
そうだろ？ シズネのねえちゃん。
ええ そのとおりよ。
Yes... that's right.
三尾の捕獲が目的じゃない。
Our goal is not to capture
the Tailed Beast.
封印して 誰も手の出せない
空間へと消えてもらう。
Even if we seal the Beast,
we will make it disappear into
a space where no one else can touch it.
それが綱手様 火影の意向よ。
That is Tsunade-sama's...
the Hokage's will.
よっしゃ やってやるぜ。
All right! Let's do it!
でもよ 尾獣って
すげぇチャクラの塊なんだろ？
But... the Tailed Beast has
a huge mass of Chakra, right?
封印ていっても ピンと来ねえけど。
I don't see how we can put a seal on it.
ええ。 尾獣を抑え込むのには
繊細なチャクラコントロールと➡
Yes. It will take an extremely
delicate amount
集中力が要求される。
of Chakra control and concentration.
(シズネ)サクラ いのは
医療忍術の習得中。
Sakura and Ino...
その経験が役に立つわ。
それから ヒナタ。
Both of you are training
in Medical Ninjutsu.
Your experience will be very useful.
あの 私には
医療忍術の経験はありません。
And Hinata...
Umm, I have no experience
in Medical Ninjutsu.
重要なのは チャクラコントロールの正確さ。
What's important is your ability
to control Chakra.
医療忍術の知識はなくとも
あなたの体得した柔拳。
You may not know Medical Ninjutsu,
but your mastery of the Gentle Fist
そして チャクラの流れを見る白眼は
役に立つ。
and your Byakugan, which can
see the flow of Chakra, will be useful.
あなたなら大丈夫よ。
ヒナタってば すげぇんだなぁ。
そ そんなこと…。
You will be fine.
Hinata, you're amazing!
N-No such thing...
わかりました。
I understand.
フーン やっぱ繊細なチャクラコントロールは➡
I guess girls are better at
delicate Chakra control. Yup, yup...
女の子の得意分野だってことだな。
うんうん。
あれ？ じゃあなんで テンテンは
封印班に選ばれてねえんだ？
Huh? But Tenten...
女の子は みんな封印班なのにさ。
How come she hasn't been chosen?
All the girls are on the Sealing team.
どうせ 私のチャクラコントロールは
ガサツよ！ ウーッ！
I guess my Chakra control is clumsy!
ちょっ
そういう意味じゃねえってばよ。
I-I didn't mean it like that!
あとのメンバーは オレとヤマトの下で
護衛担当だ。
The rest of you will work under Yamato
and I to provide protection.
まぁ 予想はしていると思うが
あの三尾を狙う連中➡
I'm sure you've already thought
about it...
こっちの封印が終わるまで
黙って見ている気はないだろう。
But those guys who are after
the Three-Tails won't sit by and watch
必ず仕掛けてくるはずだ。
while we finish sealing the beast.
They are bound to attack.
あの晶遁使いたちか。
Those guys with the Crystal Style user!
望むところです。
で 班分けは どうなるんですか？
Bring them on!
How will we team up for this?
それについてなんだけどね
ちょっと オレに考えがあって。
Yeah, about that...
I have an idea.
もったいぶってないで
教えてくれよ。
C'mon, don't hold back. Tell us!
この戦闘で 最も重要なのは
あの晶遁使いを止めること。
The most critical part of this battle
is to stop the Crystal Style user.
だが 全員がかりじゃ➡
However, if we all confront her,
the Sealing team won't have protection...
肝心の封印班を
守ることはできない。
そこで 一班を晶遁使い専門の
部隊にしようと思ったわけ。
So I'm thinking of splitting up
this team into two,
with one team focusing on her.
ナルト サイ シノ。
Naruto, Sai, Shino!
はい。
よっしゃぁ！
- Right!
- Gotcha!
以上の３名はオレの下につき
対晶遁部隊として 事に当たる。
You three will work under me
to fight the Crystal Style user!
残りの連中は…
ヤマト お前たちでやってくれ。
As for the rest...
Yamato, you guys take care of them.
わかりました。
じゃあ 今呼ばれなかった面々
集合！
Understood...
Okay, those of you who
weren't called, gather 'round!
(テンテン)
なんか 人を残りもんみたいに…。
He makes it sound like
we're the rejects...
まあまあ 青春の情熱で
がんばりましょう。
Now, now...
ああ。
ワン。
Let's go for it with
the eagerness of youth!
Yeah...
なにをしてたんだ？
What were you doing?
決まっているだろう。
Isn't it obvious?
カブト… さんに 木ノ葉の動きを
報告していたのさ。
I was reporting to Kabuto...
about the movements of the Leaf.
それと カブトさんは 一度➡
And... Kabuto-san said he was going back
to see Orochimaru-sama immediately.
大蛇丸様の元に
戻ると言っていたな。
このタイミングでか？
まぁ いろいろあるんだろうさ。
At a time like this...?
Well, I guess he has lots of things
on his mind.
そうか… 麟児。
ん？
I see...
Rinji...
さっきの話だが オレは信じる。
え？
Huh?
About earlier, I believe you...
《三尾封印の阻止と
木ノ葉の殲滅。
Preventing the sealing
of the Three-Tails,
これは 忙しくなりそうだ》
and the destruction of the Hidden Leaf.
Things are gonna get busy about now.
《木ノ葉がいる。
The Hidden Leaf are here...
まずは木ノ葉を殲滅して
三尾の捕獲はそのあとだな》
First, we have to destroy them.
Capturing Three-Tails comes after that.
《どうだっていいじゃないか。
Hah! Who cares?
私は大蛇丸様に期待されてるんだ。
Orochimaru-sama has
high hopes for me.
私の願いは 望みは
大蛇丸様と一緒になること》
My wish... my wish is to be
with Orochimaru-sama.
((大蛇丸ってヤツ 目的のためなら
どんなことだってする。
And this guy Orochimaru will do
anything to achieve his ambitions.
人の命だって
なんとも思わねえ クソ野郎だ。
He's a bastard who thinks nothing
of taking peoples' lives!
(そんなヤツについてるようなヤツが
まともな人間なわけがねえ！))
Anyone who serves a guy like
that can't be a decent human being!
《クソッ なんなんだよ》
Damn! What's wrong with me...?
こんなところで
作戦でも練っていたんですか？
What're you doing in a place like this?
Thinking up strategy?
《コイツ いつの間に？》
This guy...
When did he show up?
まあな。
《いつからいたんだ？》
Sort of...
フッ。
How long has he been here?
おや 霧が晴れてきましたね。
Oh... the mist is clearing.
ああ 出撃だ。
Yes, it's time to move!
全員 だいたいの流れは
頭に入ったわね。
All of you, have you memorized
the plan of action?
例の子供については
作戦続行中も➡
If that child is discovered during
our operation, protect him.
発見次第 保護するように。
では これより
作戦行動に入ります。
All right, let's begin.
Tenten, please show it to us.
テンテン 例のものを。
はい。
Yes.
三尾封印用に 特別に綱手様が
用意してくれた 特大巻物よ。
This is the giant scroll that was
specially prepared by Tsunade-sama
for the sealing of the Three-Tails!
はい ナルト。
Here! Naruto!
ウハァ こんなバカでけぇ巻物
使うのかよ？
Huh?! We're gonna use
this humongous scroll?
ええ そう。
Yes. We have to suppress
a huge amount of Chakra.
超強力なチャクラを抑え込まなきゃ
ならないためにね。
(シズネ)それでは カカシさん 頼みます。
Kakashi, we're counting on you.
了解。
You got it!
じゃあ 護衛班二班も
配置につくぞ。
Guard Team Two,
in your positions!
(テンテン/キバ)オオーッ。
オッス。
- Right!
ナルト ここからは別行動ね。
頼んだわよ。
Naruto! We go our separate ways now.
Good luck.
ああ 任せておけ。
Yeah!
Leave it to me!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
oh my god oh my god
yesterday's mistake got me discouraged, but
kinou no shippai de kojiketatte
Thank you! Thank you!
gottsuanda gottsuanda
my new clothes got splashed with some sauce, wow
onyuu no fuku ni sousu ga hanete wao
don't mind, don't mind, if I stay feeling like this I'll have a tear in my eyes
donmai donmai shizunda mama ja namida mo my eyes
I may be hungry and angry
donna ni hangurii de angurii demo
but I'll grab a bowl to eat and start dancing!
donburi kutte danshingu
We'll always be pals my brother!
orera itsumo demo nakama daro burazaa
hit me with an upwind or strong wind or a storm I'm ready so come on!
tatoe gyarufuu kyoufuu arashi ga fuitemo bacchikoi kamon
we may be apart but we'll still be under the same sky
hanaretetemo onaji sora no shita de
so smile and hang on
saa waratte funbatte
lets do it do it do it do it
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
even if morning doesn't come, yay yay
tatoe asa ga konakutatte yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
we'll still watch the dream together, yay yay
kimi to tomo ni yume wo miru ze yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
no matter what, don't ever, ever give up, yay yay
nani ga nandemo aa demo kou demo akirameru na yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
morning will always come after night, yay yay
donna yoru mo asa wa kuru ze yay yay
nanananana
Next Episode
Okay, then we'll maintain
this Chakra balance,
and slowly enlarge the opening.
If the Three-Tails is below the barrier,
we'll get a reaction.
Just a minute!
If we continue with such
delicate Chakra Control
and the enemy appears,
we won't be able to oppose them.
I'm already aware of that!
We won't have to fight back.
Believe in your comrades
to take care of the enemy.
You just concentrate on
your Chakra Control.
The Four-Corner Sealing Barrier
Next time: "The Four-Corner Sealing Barrier"